This is baby Amanda. She had no idea that one day she would grow up and the man she cared for
would punch her in the face. This is four-year-old Amanda. She had no idea that one day she grew up
and the man she loved would chokeslam her. This is eight-year-old Amanda who would one day consume
a lot of liquor and then get taken advantage of. This is 12-year-old Amanda who didn't know that
one day she'd be mushed by a man she cared about. This is 16-year-old Amanda who didn't know that
one day she'd be stolen from by several men she cared about. This is 26-year-old Amanda who didn't
know that one day she'd be having a miscarriage and her partner would leave her at the hospital.
This is 39-year-old Amanda who didn't know that someday soon she would be sexually assaulted
in a hotel room while her partner lay asleep in the bed next to her. And this is 44-year-old Amanda
who understands that there is no dollar amount that would cure any of that trauma. Who understands
that when we seek justice and accountability it does not equate to healing. Money, jail sentences
are all simply deterrents that society has come up with to try to quell the abuse from continuing.
While it continues to perpetuate the falsehood that women are objects and lesser than. All of us
were once young people in a world that has been waiting for us and we are trying to find our way
through. And in that process we face those who harm us and we try our best to get to the other side.
Knowing that no matter how much money abusers are forced to pay or how much jail time they are forced
to serve. It does not make them less likely to abuse and it does not heal them from what caused
them to become abusers in the first place. It does not change that we are tasked with working on not
how to get over but how to get through. Because no matter what they tell you this life is long.
And even with all the abuse that I've suffered and so many of us have suffered. I carry no bitterness
towards men. I carry a purpose to make a world that does not create men who think like this.